<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AIESEC</string>
    <string name="fragment1text">Hello, this is AISEC VIt chapter. We do a lot of work related to a lot of people and we go to places and hangout all over the world</string>
    <string name="about_aiesec_content">AIESEC is the world’s largest youth run organization which has been activating potential for 69 years  and has approximately 70,000 members in 126 countries and territories and has delivered over  480,000 experiences to date. \n\n We are a non-governmental not-for- profit organization that has been endorsed by the United  Nations, multiple presidents world-wide, CEOs of multinational corporations and recognised by  UNESCO.</string>
    <string name="about_aiesec">About AIESEC</string>
    <string name="about_vision">OUR VISION</string>
    <string name="aiesec_vision_content">Our vision and motto is “We strive to achieve peace and fulfilment of humankind’s potential.” by  providing the youth a platform to develop their leadership skills and promoting cross-cultural global  exchanges with a focus of creating a positive impact on society. \n\n We believe that it is every young person’s responsibility to take a positive role shaping the future of  our planet and everyone deserves the chance, and tools, to fulfil their potential. We provide young  people with self-driven, practical, global experiences. We empower them to see the world, have a  genuine effect and find what really matters to them.</string>

    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="files">Files</string>
    <string name="directories">Folders</string>
    <string name="goUp">Go Up</string>
    <string name="all">Check All</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="none">Uncheck All</string>
    <string name="ext">External</string>
    <string name="Int">Internal</string>
    <string name="New">New Folder</string>
    <string name="CNew">Enter New Folder Name</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ogvtext">Global Volunteer is an intensive international volunteer abroad experience that enables you to work on projects that impact social issues. Through this we empower communities by developing the people and enabling them to develop a more sustainable and healthy future.
Overall, through this program, AIESEC is providing young students an opportunity to develop entrepreneurial and leadership skills through international internships mainly on social issues which will help them enrich their education, challenge their worldview and help them gain a unique combination of multi cultural, social and entrepreneurial experience during the formative years of their lives.
We have a wide range of more than 20 countries with Global Volunteering projects in store.
</string>

    <string name="ogetText">Outgoing Global Entrepreneur provides a platform for enabling transformation through an entrepreneurial experience in start up environments abroad. The duration of the experience ranges from 6 weeks until 12 weeks. Depending on the project accepted for, a stipend may or may not be provided. Are you ready to venture into the world full of
opportunities unexplored?
In the race to be better than the best, we need to do things even best can not imagine. Taking the road less travelled is not just a myth anymore. Technical internships abroad is the way forward to stand out.
Outgoing Global Talent allows you to work for 3 to 18 months in a corporate environment with regards to various fields of interests with a regulated stipend
depending on the project accepted for.
With flexible timelines and a world full of possibilities what are you waiting for?</string>
    <string name="tab_1">Profile</string>
    <string name="tab_2">Documents</string>
    <string name="tab_3">Resources</string>
    <string name="expansions">Our expansion entities: \n\n\n
    CMC\n
    Erode\n\n
        
    If you are interested in partnering with us, contact us on prithvi.kumar@aiesec.net
    </string>


    <string-array name="admin_choices">
        <item>Enter your choice</item>
        <item>Execution Body</item>
        <item>Managament Body</item>
        <item>General Body</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_aiesec_main">AiesecMainActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="icxtext">It is a big beautiful world, isn\'t it? What limits our understanding of this world are stereotypes and how we form opinions without seeing things for ourselves. AIESEC demands to change this, we believe in our youth to be fair. Incoming Exchange, is the department that ensures people from across oceans have a chance to stay with us, to help us grow while we help them grow. These people who come here are called Exchange Participants, these people, we believe, our unique.</string>

</resources>

    <!--The duration of the experience ranges from 6 weeks until 12 weeks. Depending on  the project accepted for, a stipend may or may not be provided. Are you ready  to venture into the world full of opportunities unexplored ?  In the race to be better than the best, we need to do things even best can&#39;t  imagine. Taking the road less travelled is not just a myth anymore. Technical  internships abroad is the way forward to stand out.  Outgoing Global Talent allows you to work for 3 to 18 months in a corporate  environment with regards to various fields of interests with a regulated stipend  depending on the project accepted for.  With flexible timelines and a world full of possibilities what are you waiting for-->
